clickinmoms.com 2019-12-01

# Privacy Policy - Click & Company

Skip to content

Privacy Policy[CMadmin](https://clickandcompany.com/author/cmadmin/ "Posts by CMadmin")2019-05-01T21:13:57+00:00

**PRIVACY POLICY**

_Updated 30 April 2019_

**About Us  
**

Click & Company (“we,” “us,” “Click & Co”) is a media, membership, and education company comprised of six daughter brands that collectively empower photographers of all levels to capture life beautifully in both their personal and professional endeavors, to make flexible, quality photography education and mentoring accessible, and to maintain a supportive community for continuous learning, sharing, and growth.  These brands include Clickin Moms, Click Magazine, Click Pro, Click Photo School, Click Away, Click & Co Store, and Let the Kids. Click & Company is located on the web at clickandcompany.com, clickinmoms.com, myclickmagazine.com, clickprophotographers.com, clickphotoschool.com, clickawayconference.com, and letthekids.com. This privacy policy provides details about how your personal information is collected, shared, and used by us.

**Information We Collect From You**

When accessing our website, Click & Company will learn certain information about you during your visit. How we will handle information we learn about you depends upon what you do when visiting our site.

**_Account Registrations, Purchases, Submissions, Mailing List Signups, and Other Transactions_**

When you sign up for a membership or subscription, purchase a product, register for a course, enter a contest, claim a prize, participate in a poll, register for a mailing list or digital download, comment on an article, or otherwise engage in a transaction or website activity or event, we may collect a variety of information, including but not limited to:

  1. Name
  2. Company name
  3. Website
  4. Mailing address
  5. Time zone
  6. Phone number
  7. Email address

Credit card transactions and Paypal purchases do not result in the transmission of your financial data to us.

_**Use of Services, Website Visits, Downloads, and Support**_

If you visit our site to read or download information on our pages, we collect and store only the following information about you:

1\. The date and time you access our site.  
2\. The name of the domain from which you access the Internet.  
3\. The Internet Protocol Address used to access our site, often referred to as IP Address.  
4\. Geographic location as indicated by your IP Address  
5\. Browser type and language.  
6\. Operating system.  
7\. Referring, visited, and exit pages.  
8\. If using a proxy, the name of the proxy in case of improper use.

_**Other Sources and Interactions**_

We may also obtain information about you, individually or in aggregate form, from other sources and interactions, such as: information you provide to us in surveys; information that is publicly available; information that you provide to us at events; information that you provide to us conversationally as part of forum threads, class discussions, focus groups, or otherwise as written or spoken feedback.

**How We Use the Collected Information**

We use the information we collect for the following purposes: 

  1. To provide the requested products and services to you. 
  2. To remember personal information for your convenience when you use our website, online services, and applications.
  3. To provide you with engaging, high-quality content.
  4. To ensure the proper functioning of our site and services. 
  5. To provide you with technical and account support.
  6. To improve our products, services, and content. 
  7. To keep you apprised of our products, events, contests, education, services, special offers, partner promos, opportunities, important notices, and more. 
  8. For statistical purposes, including the assessment of visitor volume and frequency to the different areas of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.  

  9. To improve site speed, security, and to improve the user experience for all customers and other visitors.
  10. To offer you targeted offers and content.
  11. To inform, optimize, and serve advertisements based on your engagement and activity on our site.
  12. In connection with our security and compliance programs, including recording opt-ins and consent.

If you identify yourself by sending us an e-mail containing personal information, then the information collected will be solely used to respond to your message.

**Disclosure to Third Parties**

Click & Company may share your personal information with our vendors and other carefully selected third parties for the purpose of fulfilling customer orders, processing payments, detecting fraud, delivering products to you, facilitating prize claims, managing and enhancing customer data, and providing customer service.

Click & Company uses services for site hosting, monitoring, and security. These services may access our website’s components, database, files, and similar so that the site performance, operation, maintenance, and troubleshooting can be protected and improved. The data shared and processed depends on the characteristics and implementation of the services rendered.

We may disclose your personal information to courts of law, law enforcement authorities and other relevant third parties when we have a good faith belief that law or public policy reasonably requires us to do so. Such disclosure may be required when you or a third party are or may be causing injury to Click & Company or third parties; violating the property or other legal rights of Click & Company or third parties; or otherwise violating federal, state, local, or other applicable law.

We may disclose personal information about you if we determine that doing so is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users.

Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale, we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

Click & Company will not sell or otherwise transfer your personal information, including email or address information, to unaffiliated third parties without your express consent at the time of collection.

**Cookies & Pixel Tags  
**  
Click & Company may use cookies and other technologies to evaluate user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of targeted advertisements and web searches. We also use these technologies to remember personal information for your convenience when you use our website, online services, and applications. 

Click & Company uses third-party service providers to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These advertising service providers use cookies and pixel tags to gather information about your interactions with our website, as well as to inform, optimize and serve targeted advertising based on those interactions.

You can learn more information about the cookies we and our partners use, as well as how to manage or opt out from cookies, in our [Cookie Information & Consent Policy.](http://clickandcompany.com/cookie-policy/)

**Affiliate Marketing**

Click & Company is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com

**Data Collection & Use Preferences and Opt-Out**

_**Email**  
_You may manage your email preferences or opt out of our marketing communications at any time by following the manage or unsubscribe link in the footer of all non-transactional email messages that we send. Some communications from us are considered transactional or service communications (such as receipts, password/account information, shipping notifications, digital downloads, accessibility information for purchased products, service/maintenance updates, legal notices, and similar) and are not subject to opt-in or opt-out requests or requirements.

_**Cookies  
**You can learn more information about the cookies we and our partners use, as well as how to manage or opt out from cookies, in our [Cookie Information & Consent Policy.](http://clickandcompany.com/cookie-policy/) **  
**_

**Protection of Personal Information**

Click & Company takes precautions including but not limited to administrative and technical measures to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

Please bear in mind that the personal information you share in your public user profile,  within the Click & Company forums, as part of a guest contributor profile, as part of a blog comment profile, and similar is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. Although our Terms of Service prohibit the copying or publication of any content posted within the Clickin Moms forums by third parties, Click & Company cannot safeguard any information you disclose in these locations, and you are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these circumstances. If you voluntarily offer any feedback, data, answers, questions, comments, suggestions, or ideas, Click & Company will treat such information as non-confidential and non-proprietary.

**Children  
**Our websites, products, and services are not directed to children, and we do not intentionally or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13.  We request that individuals under the age of 13 not submit any personal information on the site.

Data Retention  
Click & Company may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Access, Correction, & Erasure**  
Upon request and when required by law (such as the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679, or GDPR), we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personally identifiable information. To request this information, or to request revision or removal of personal attribution or other personally identifiable information from our site, please contact us at support@clickandcompany.com. Please note that we will require you to verify your identity before responding to any requests to exercise your rights by providing details only known to the account holder. Where you request correction, please explain in detail why you believe the personal information we hold about you to be inaccurate or incomplete so that we can assess whether a correction is required. We will respond to these requests within a reasonable timeframe, and we will remove, revise, or anonymize this information on your behalf as may be required by law.
